<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<co3h>
   <asynchronous>
      <youtube_video id="57">
         <async_info>
            <publisher>coppertropicals</publisher>
            <video_title>8/24/19 Noon Earthquake Update Dutchsinse</video_title>
            <video_description>Subscribe to dutchsince backup channel https://www.youtube.com/user/dutchsince
Live stream viewable at https://twitch.tv/dutchsinseofficial   or
https://dlive.tv/Dutchsinse or
https://mixer.com/Dutchsinse or
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCg3X5jbW7tzkkPeY2pNX-7g
Subscriber Chat Rules: No attacking other chatters or channels, if you have personal problems with other chatters, take it private between yourselves, or better to just NOT engage in conflicts in the paid chat. People are paying to be in the chat, all subscribers, VIPs and moderators are expected to be courteous, and kind to each other at all times. No spamming, no promotion of other channels unless authorized by Dutchsinse, no excessive zealotry (anti-religion or pro-religion), minimal politics, and PG13 level swearing - non-sexual, and non-racial. Try to stick on topic of earthquakes, and similar geophysics topics. Subscribers who violate chat rules will first receive ONE warning, then a time out for 10 min if it happens again, if beyond a 2nd violation, any person (moderator, vip, or paying subscriber) may be permanently banned by the channel owner / moderators.*




Earthquakes can systematically trigger other ones on opposite side of Earth (antipodes)

antipode earthquakes on the opposite sides of the planet

Professionals now adopting &quot;GLOBAL EARTHQUAKE FORECASTING MODELS&quot; which have been proved correct:

http://temblor.net/earthquake-insights/global-earthquake-forecast-passes-test-7247/

*Disclaimer* Before sharing the information contained in this video, please consult local, and national laws in your country to verify if you are allowed to share earthquake warnings from private individual

disclaimer The comments seen on the 24/7 earthquake live stream are not endorsed by, nor do they reflect the views of the creator of this channel. All comments are assumed to be the responsibility of the end user who caused the generation of text, emojis, or symbols of any kind in chat ( or by whatever means the characters presented are generated).

Southern California Slow Slip article + Studies

Monitor Slow Slip tremors in the Pacific Northwest: https://tunk.ess.washington.edu/map_display/

Search Antipodes (opposite sides of the planet) here: https://www.antipodesmap.com/

Download the full (paid) version of earthquake3D here :
http://www.wolton.net/quakes.html

Download the &quot;arrow map&quot; graphic for personal use.. (.tga file), only can be used in full version of Earthquake3D : http://www.mediafire.com/file/juy1u7b47z0p2i1/PublicDownload1.4MED.tga/file

Free version here:

http://www.wolton.net/quake.html

Earthquake3D interactive live feed :

http://www.earthquake3d.com/

We (dutchsinse and viewers) are not associated with Earthquake3D's creation, maintenance, or development. We receive no compensation for recommending this application, and have no relation with (or to) the programs developer(s).

If you would like the full paid version, please purchase a copy directly from the program creators website which is linked above, so they receive full compensation for the hard work they put in creating this wonderful seismic monitoring program!

Earthquake Resources:

Check tsunami warnings issued by the US agencies here:

http://tsunami.gov/

Pacific Tsunami Warning Center:

http://ptwc.weather.gov/

Alaska Tsunami Warning Center:

http://wcatwc.arh.noaa.gov/

National Data Buoy Center (NDBC) buoy monitoring:

http://www.ndbc.noaa.gov/

Deep-ocean Assessment Reporting Tsunamis (DART) buoys:

http://www.ndbc.noaa.gov/dart.shtml

Global Earthquake Monitoring Links (multiple agencies worldwide):

https://sincedutch.wordpress.com/2011/11/30/11302011-list-of-earthquake-links-for-global-monitoring/

USGS main earthquake reporting site:

https://earthquake.usgs.gov

European / EMSC main earthquake reporting site:

https://www.emsc-csem.org/Earthquake/

New Zealand Earthquakes:

http://www.geonet.org.nz/

Japan Earthquakes:

http://www.jma.go.jp/en/quake/

Live streaming Japan earthquakes:

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCyMW-_pfjsTG76c9tP5SErg

Volcanic Ash Advisory Center (VAAC):

https://www.volcanodiscovery.com/news/vaac/latest-reports.html

The non-earthquake related graphics, images, background, content , video, voice content captured on this property , and which are on this stream are NOT intended for redistribution, copying, or repeating unless otherwise approved by the content creator, Michael Janitch aka Dutchsinse.

Marker height off the globe represents depth into the Earth.

When an earthquake strikes, you will hear a rumble, ding, and a bell toll. The bell will toll the number of times = to the earthquake which occurs. (example : M4.0 will ring 4 times).

The most recent earthquake has a green placemark / flag on it.

Blue flag / placemark = the last earthquake which was looked up

--- Michael Janitch - PO Box 1562 - Marthasville, MO 63357</video_description>
            <date>2019-08-24</date>
            <time>18:40:11.000Z</time>
            <total_views>12602</total_views>
            <likes>1478</likes>
            <dislikes>17</dislikes>
            <favourites>0</favourites>
            <total_comments>289</total_comments>
            <audio_language>NA</audio_language>
         </async_info>
         <main_content>
            <original_script name="Roman">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SG7Qp9WGPjU</original_script>
         </main_content>
         <async_comment id="1">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Thunder Cloud Jern</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-27</published_date>
               <published_time>07:53:22.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-27</final_date>
               <final_time>07:53:22.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>21</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Where&amp;#39;s it stop. Hola Mexico California. Fabulous. Baha to Juan De Fuca. Don&amp;#39;t report Cali. They be camping on Dr beach.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Where's it stop. Hola Mexico California. Fabulous. Baha to Juan De Fuca. Don't report Cali. They be camping on Dr beach.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="2">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Thunder Cloud Jern</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-27</published_date>
               <published_time>07:44:46.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-27</final_date>
               <final_time>07:44:46.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>29</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Glad to see you. How about going personal. You tube is obviously cooperating with USGS..&lt;br /&gt;Use gmail site. Ha! Sure Coppertone can fill this report on email and gmail.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Glad to see you. How about going personal. You tube is obviously cooperating with USGS..
Use gmail site. Ha! Sure Coppertone can fill this report on email and gmail.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="3">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Jessica Camillo</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>17:07:48.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>17:07:48.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>193</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">No Dutch I would NEVER let the people who support me down. EVER. Screw them Dutch we have all had your back and it&amp;#39;s pretty messed up to punish us. I&amp;#39;ve literally been on the USGS Facebook , you can look for yourself on the post about the recent Ridgecrest 5.0.standing up for you, so you saying this really kinda hurts actually. I understand your frustrations, I do. But if you stop doing what you do, guess what... You do nothing more but let them win. And I&amp;#39;ve truly been speaking out for you on the USGS Facebook. Please pull yourself together. In my honest opinion, I&amp;#39;d stop mentioning them or hell anyone else for that matter. COMPLETELY ACT AS IF THEY DON&amp;#39;T EXIST. This will keep you out of trouble and make a statement loud and clear. I feel like I might actually be the cause of your recent troubles because I was standing up for you. So if that is the case, I will apologize for causing you stress however, I will not stop speaking out until one of them listen. You deserve to be heard and deserve to be recognized.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>No Dutch I would NEVER let the people who support me down. EVER. Screw them Dutch we have all had your back and it's pretty messed up to punish us. I've literally been on the USGS Facebook , you can look for yourself on the post about the recent Ridgecrest 5.0.standing up for you, so you saying this really kinda hurts actually. I understand your frustrations, I do. But if you stop doing what you do, guess what... You do nothing more but let them win. And I've truly been speaking out for you on the USGS Facebook. Please pull yourself together. In my honest opinion, I'd stop mentioning them or hell anyone else for that matter. COMPLETELY ACT AS IF THEY DON'T EXIST. This will keep you out of trouble and make a statement loud and clear. I feel like I might actually be the cause of your recent troubles because I was standing up for you. So if that is the case, I will apologize for causing you stress however, I will not stop speaking out until one of them listen. You deserve to be heard and deserve to be recognized.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="4">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Anna Durkee</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>16:58:24.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>16:58:24.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>27</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">my husband and I felt a deep deep vibration under the earth last night around midnight..it came in waves and very strange.What was that in washington state.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>my husband and I felt a deep deep vibration under the earth last night around midnight..it came in waves and very strange.What was that in washington state.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="5">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Mary McCracken</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>16:48:30.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>16:48:30.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>14</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">They just suck so bad the way they naff with you. Love you Dutch.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>They just suck so bad the way they naff with you. Love you Dutch.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="6">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Jessica Camillo</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>16:38:34.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>16:38:34.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>21</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Dutch I was standing up for you on the USGS Facebook page. On the post ABOUT THE 5.0 ! Soooo..... Ya.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Dutch I was standing up for you on the USGS Facebook page. On the post ABOUT THE 5.0 ! Soooo..... Ya.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="7">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Jessica Camillo</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>16:37:20.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>16:37:20.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>23</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Dutch it&amp;#39;s Monday and la Jolla CA just had a 2.4 sooo I&amp;#39;m thinking energy might be transferring to the Diego area ???</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Dutch it's Monday and la Jolla CA just had a 2.4 sooo I'm thinking energy might be transferring to the Diego area ???</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="8">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Astrafire1</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>10:59:24.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>10:59:57.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>1</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>34</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">In my opinion blocking your early warnings is no different than intentional attempted murder.  Lives are saved because of you Dutch. If anything bad happens because you&amp;#39;re blocked the blood is on their hands.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>In my opinion blocking your early warnings is no different than intentional attempted murder.  Lives are saved because of you Dutch. If anything bad happens because you're blocked the blood is on their hands.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="9">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Chandra Mohammed</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>10:58:34.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>10:58:34.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>42</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Hey dutch dont ever give up or give in..... thats what they want.... dont let them break you and keep doing whats right... keep strong and much love to you and your family.... i also had a hard time finding your videos....🤗🤗🤗🤗</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Hey dutch dont ever give up or give in..... thats what they want.... dont let them break you and keep doing whats right... keep strong and much love to you and your family.... i also had a hard time finding your videos....🤗🤗🤗🤗</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="10">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Skye Angel</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>10:23:11.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>10:23:11.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>31</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Copper Tat’s stream blocked to UK viewers (all together saying video has been blocked in your country) can’t get there via Dutch either thought I should let you know ML ❤️</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Copper Tat’s stream blocked to UK viewers (all together saying video has been blocked in your country) can’t get there via Dutch either thought I should let you know ML ❤️</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="11">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Skye Angel</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>09:44:57.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>09:44:57.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>62</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">It takes a Wisdom &amp;amp; Maturity; most don’t have, to overcome you’re own stubbornness, raise yourself above &amp;amp; still have the generosity of spirit to continue in the face of adversity. That’s why I’ve stuck around last near Decade because you continued beyond your own obligation that’s Special Dutch/Tat in doing so you’ve created a Family here too Respect &amp;amp; MLA ❤️</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>It takes a Wisdom &amp; Maturity; most don’t have, to overcome you’re own stubbornness, raise yourself above &amp; still have the generosity of spirit to continue in the face of adversity. That’s why I’ve stuck around last near Decade because you continued beyond your own obligation that’s Special Dutch/Tat in doing so you’ve created a Family here too Respect &amp; MLA ❤️</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="12">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Phyllis Westbury</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>09:40:22.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>09:40:22.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>17</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">What you you tell your family? Lol. Yes. Don’t stop warning people. You are doing great 👍</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>What you you tell your family? Lol. Yes. Don’t stop warning people. You are doing great 👍</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="13">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Phyllis Westbury</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>09:28:52.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>09:28:52.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>5</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Says private on Dutch’s page</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Says private on Dutch’s page</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="14">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Skye Angel</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>09:22:52.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>09:22:52.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>21</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Dutch &amp;amp; Copper You’re Amazing, your TruthPrints; Vital Information. TY for all you do. Blessings &amp;amp; Love to you All ❤️</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Dutch &amp; Copper You’re Amazing, your TruthPrints; Vital Information. TY for all you do. Blessings &amp; Love to you All ❤️</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="15">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Bonita Jordan</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>07:53:06.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>07:53:06.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>1</replies>
               <words>22</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Dutch can you check out Blackpool UK. Looks like they’ve had another earthquake today possibly a 3( Monday) Quadrilla is fracking again!</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Dutch can you check out Blackpool UK. Looks like they’ve had another earthquake today possibly a 3( Monday) Quadrilla is fracking again!</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="15.1">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Chris Jones</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-29</published_date>
               <published_time>23:04:37.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-29</final_date>
               <final_time>23:04:37.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <words>9</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Had them everyday. None stop. Now up to. 3.0</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Had them everyday. None stop. Now up to. 3.0</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="16">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Scott Cowen</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>06:33:42.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>06:33:42.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>42</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Well I will give a forecast there is a chastisement from God comming everyone needs to convert to Jesus&amp;#39;s church, the catholic church, follow the laws of God and pray and do penance &lt;br /&gt;May God have mercy on us all&lt;br /&gt;Micha&amp;#39;EL</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Well I will give a forecast there is a chastisement from God comming everyone needs to convert to Jesus's church, the catholic church, follow the laws of God and pray and do penance 
May God have mercy on us all
Micha'EL</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="17">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Bonnie Anderson</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>05:16:59.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>05:16:59.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>24</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Thx you copper for always being there for Dutch man. Just wanted to tell you how much we appreciate you. Much love and blessings.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Thx you copper for always being there for Dutch man. Just wanted to tell you how much we appreciate you. Much love and blessings.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="18">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Michael Blackwell</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>04:52:43.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>04:52:43.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>53</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Is there anyone on here from California that left due to Earthquake events lately? Anyone at all? Or are all of you just going to wait until it pops and take your chances?&lt;br /&gt;Please don&amp;#39;t make excuses. Excuses can&amp;#39;t save you when there&amp;#39;s nowhere to run and no fuel to leave. Jus&amp;#39; sayin&amp;#39;.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Is there anyone on here from California that left due to Earthquake events lately? Anyone at all? Or are all of you just going to wait until it pops and take your chances?
Please don't make excuses. Excuses can't save you when there's nowhere to run and no fuel to leave. Jus' sayin'.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="19">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Carolyn Lanier Roberts</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>04:42:35.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>04:42:35.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>3</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">You are Awesome!</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>You are Awesome!</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="20">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Richard Lowry</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-08-26</published_date>
               <published_time>04:36:37.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-08-26</final_date>
               <final_time>04:36:37.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>16</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Dutch, they screening your forecast brings more attention on your abilities, and they being inept .</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Dutch, they screening your forecast brings more attention on your abilities, and they being inept .</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
      </youtube_video>
   </asynchronous>
</co3h>
