<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<co3h>
   <asynchronous>
      <youtube_video id="25">
         <async_info>
            <publisher>BBC News</publisher>
            <video_title>Hong Kong protests: Knife attacker bites man's ear after stabbing four - BBC News</video_title>
            <video_description>Five people have been injured in a knife attack at the site of a pro-democracy protest in Hong Kong.

The attack happened at the Cityplaza mall in the Tai Koo district on Hong Kong Island.

The local hospital authority said four men and one woman were injured, with two in critical condition.

One of the injured, a local councillor, had his ear partially bitten off by the as-yet unidentified male attacker, who was subdued by passersby in the mall.

Please subscribe HERE http://bit.ly/1rbfUog</video_description>
            <date>2019-11-04</date>
            <time>10:42:10.000Z</time>
            <total_views>62762</total_views>
            <likes>506</likes>
            <dislikes>101</dislikes>
            <favourites>0</favourites>
            <total_comments>579</total_comments>
            <audio_language>en-GB</audio_language>
         </async_info>
         <main_content>
            <original_script name="Roman">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ml5XRDVkQF4</original_script>
         </main_content>
         <async_comment id="1">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Jony Chandra</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-09</published_date>
               <published_time>06:07:34.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-09</final_date>
               <final_time>06:07:34.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>2</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Idiot millenial.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Idiot millenial.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="2">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>John Smith</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-08</published_date>
               <published_time>07:06:21.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-08</final_date>
               <final_time>07:06:21.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>19</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">These are pro democracy supporter for bbc..   They look like criminals. In USA police have already been shots them.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>These are pro democracy supporter for bbc..   They look like criminals. In USA police have already been shots them.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="3">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>buddy man</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-08</published_date>
               <published_time>02:06:47.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-08</final_date>
               <final_time>02:06:47.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>22</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">If u don&amp;#39;t like to be Chinese. Just move out from east and go to west. Don&amp;#39;t forget Change your Chinese face</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>If u don't like to be Chinese. Just move out from east and go to west. Don't forget Change your Chinese face</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="4">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Peter Le</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>21:51:36.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>21:51:36.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>35</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Pray for not happening to U.S the future if we take God off will happen for sure I pray for all Christened brother sister in Hong Kong love and peace on them all God bless</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Pray for not happening to U.S the future if we take God off will happen for sure I pray for all Christened brother sister in Hong Kong love and peace on them all God bless</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="5">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Modus Operandi</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>21:13:29.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>21:13:29.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>23</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Brags about democracy and rule of law, yet they can&amp;#39;t prosecute a paedophile &amp;quot;prince&amp;quot;? Good thing Israel is keep everyone on their leash.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Brags about democracy and rule of law, yet they can't prosecute a paedophile &quot;prince&quot;? Good thing Israel is keep everyone on their leash.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="6">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>LIDYAEIL</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>19:06:47.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>19:06:47.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>23</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">So these protesting teenagers run to police when they need their help and want police to be disbanded when they commit crimes.... mature</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>So these protesting teenagers run to police when they need their help and want police to be disbanded when they commit crimes.... mature</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="7">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Cross</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>13:56:31.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>13:56:31.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>1</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>18</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">I don&amp;#39;t care who u are, ur stabbing and biting ppl&amp;#39;s ears off u deserve to get shot</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>I don't care who u are, ur stabbing and biting ppl's ears off u deserve to get shot</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="8">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Kiara V</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>13:08:57.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>13:08:57.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>6</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>8</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">you should say protesters pointing  lasers at police</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>you should say protesters pointing  lasers at police</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="9">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>levi L</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>12:54:27.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>12:54:27.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>4</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>21</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Support the reunification of Ireland, the independence of Wales, the independence of Scotland and the independence of every village in England</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Support the reunification of Ireland, the independence of Wales, the independence of Scotland and the independence of every village in England</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="10">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>John Koh</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>05:31:40.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>05:31:40.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>7</replies>
               <words>17</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Guess what? Democracy has failed in HK.&lt;br /&gt;The only thing works is FreeDOOM Fighters which rules HK.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Guess what? Democracy has failed in HK.
The only thing works is FreeDOOM Fighters which rules HK.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="10.1">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>LokYin Yun</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-09</published_date>
               <published_time>13:51:54.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-09</final_date>
               <final_time>13:51:54.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <words>143</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">@John Koh I&amp;#39;m going to backtrack a bit and say you&amp;#39;re right, HK never had the right to govern themselves when it was a colony, partially because that&amp;#39;s how colonies work. You know whats also true? The people don&amp;#39;t have the right to elect their own Chief Executive either.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hk is part of China, except it&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;one country, two system&amp;#39;. Chapter 1, article 5 of the Basic Law, quote &amp;#39;The socialist system and policies shall not be practiced in the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region, and the previous capitalist system and way of life shall remain unchanged for 50 years.&amp;#39;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not even going to discuss Singapore because that&amp;#39;s straying way too off topic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It&amp;#39;s an entire staff of the bookstore that got abducted by Chinese authority, of which one was forced to admit his &amp;#39;crimes&amp;#39; on CCTV.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>@John Koh I'm going to backtrack a bit and say you're right, HK never had the right to govern themselves when it was a colony, partially because that's how colonies work. You know whats also true? The people don't have the right to elect their own Chief Executive either.


Hk is part of China, except it's 'one country, two system'. Chapter 1, article 5 of the Basic Law, quote 'The socialist system and policies shall not be practiced in the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region, and the previous capitalist system and way of life shall remain unchanged for 50 years.'


Not even going to discuss Singapore because that's straying way too off topic.


It's an entire staff of the bookstore that got abducted by Chinese authority, of which one was forced to admit his 'crimes' on CCTV.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="10.2">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>John Koh</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-08</published_date>
               <published_time>22:33:37.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-08</final_date>
               <final_time>22:33:37.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <words>136</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">@LokYin Yun&lt;br /&gt;You fail to admit Britain had never given HK freedom to govern themselves for 150 years. Your Hypocrisy is obvious.&lt;br /&gt;You fail to recognise the fact HK is part of China. I suppose You never read history book. &lt;br /&gt;Democracy fails in HK, one good example is where rich capitalism prevails as 4 filthy rich HK families control much of HK land bank. HK people get use to living in cages since the British rules. &lt;br /&gt;Whereas Singapore LKY, a socialist authoritarian &amp;amp; critic of democracy, implemented undemocratic policy to ensure youths can afford housing. He controls western news, freedom of speech, locked up &amp;amp; banish political dissidents. Yet Singapore thrives despite being undemocratic.&lt;br /&gt;I thought HK book seller is nothing but a opportunist to defame Chinese leader. BTW, Who will buy his story?</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>@LokYin Yun
You fail to admit Britain had never given HK freedom to govern themselves for 150 years. Your Hypocrisy is obvious.
You fail to recognise the fact HK is part of China. I suppose You never read history book. 
Democracy fails in HK, one good example is where rich capitalism prevails as 4 filthy rich HK families control much of HK land bank. HK people get use to living in cages since the British rules. 
Whereas Singapore LKY, a socialist authoritarian &amp; critic of democracy, implemented undemocratic policy to ensure youths can afford housing. He controls western news, freedom of speech, locked up &amp; banish political dissidents. Yet Singapore thrives despite being undemocratic.
I thought HK book seller is nothing but a opportunist to defame Chinese leader. BTW, Who will buy his story?</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="10.3">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>LokYin Yun</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-08</published_date>
               <published_time>16:28:00.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-08</final_date>
               <final_time>16:28:00.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <words>176</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">@John Koh I love how this discussion of &amp;#39;democracy has failed in HK&amp;#39; took a sharp turn to &amp;#39;list all the bad things colonialism does&amp;#39;, but sure, I will continue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There&amp;#39;s no need for locals to get involved when the governor is implementing policies that benefit the people. Stuff like education and housing. Don&amp;#39;t play identity politics with me. It&amp;#39;s only after the handover that every CEs have attempted to assimilate the future generation to the mainland, and not fully addressing the needs of the people. &lt;br /&gt;Did the rioters care when they plant bombs and killed innocent people, including children, or state media threatening an invasion? Or that time militia across the border shot and killed police officers?&lt;br /&gt;Again, it&amp;#39;s hell of a luxurious slavery when the people are enjoying all the perks of a first world nation.&lt;br /&gt;Also, universal suffrage is promised in the Basic Law of HK. &lt;br /&gt;Freedoms taken by China? Gee I don&amp;#39;t know, but is &amp;#39;kidnapping and convicting booksellers selling books party officials don&amp;#39;t like one of them?&amp;#39;</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>@John Koh I love how this discussion of 'democracy has failed in HK' took a sharp turn to 'list all the bad things colonialism does', but sure, I will continue.


There's no need for locals to get involved when the governor is implementing policies that benefit the people. Stuff like education and housing. Don't play identity politics with me. It's only after the handover that every CEs have attempted to assimilate the future generation to the mainland, and not fully addressing the needs of the people. 
Did the rioters care when they plant bombs and killed innocent people, including children, or state media threatening an invasion? Or that time militia across the border shot and killed police officers?
Again, it's hell of a luxurious slavery when the people are enjoying all the perks of a first world nation.
Also, universal suffrage is promised in the Basic Law of HK. 
Freedoms taken by China? Gee I don't know, but is 'kidnapping and convicting booksellers selling books party officials don't like one of them?'</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="10.4">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>John Koh</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-08</published_date>
               <published_time>10:34:48.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-08</final_date>
               <final_time>10:34:48.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <words>75</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">@LokYin Yun&lt;br /&gt;Did Britain give any minister posts, senior government position &amp;amp; governor post to HK people?&lt;br /&gt;Did British care about HK when they shot at rioters?&lt;br /&gt;1982? Too little too late after 150 years of slavery. &lt;br /&gt;China &amp;amp; HK government are too kind to give Hkroachs a second chance. &lt;br /&gt;The fact remains the same, it is a Quasi-constituitional government just in case you don&amp;#39;t agree. &lt;br /&gt;Name those freedoms taken by China?</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>@LokYin Yun
Did Britain give any minister posts, senior government position &amp; governor post to HK people?
Did British care about HK when they shot at rioters?
1982? Too little too late after 150 years of slavery. 
China &amp; HK government are too kind to give Hkroachs a second chance. 
The fact remains the same, it is a Quasi-constituitional government just in case you don't agree. 
Name those freedoms taken by China?</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="10.5">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>LokYin Yun</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-08</published_date>
               <published_time>09:27:35.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-08</final_date>
               <final_time>09:27:35.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <words>93</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">@John Koh &amp;#39;China allows HK...govern themselves&amp;#39; Um, not quite. It was the Sino-British joint declaration. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#39;Britain never given them freedom to govern themselves&amp;#39; There were local elections as back as 1982. Also, the colonial government back then did a fairly good job in turning a city prosperous and free.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#39;150 years slavery&amp;#39; We had uncensored internet, freedom of the press, wealth and got to see the world, while across the border intellectuals are sent to work in farms and landlords murdered. So I&amp;#39;ll say there&amp;#39;s quite a big hole in your cage.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>@John Koh 'China allows HK...govern themselves' Um, not quite. It was the Sino-British joint declaration. 
'Britain never given them freedom to govern themselves' There were local elections as back as 1982. Also, the colonial government back then did a fairly good job in turning a city prosperous and free.
'150 years slavery' We had uncensored internet, freedom of the press, wealth and got to see the world, while across the border intellectuals are sent to work in farms and landlords murdered. So I'll say there's quite a big hole in your cage.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="11">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Terence senior Ng</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>04:05:19.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>04:05:19.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>1</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">你把它耳朵摇掉它也听得到把它眼球挖出来他就看不到</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>你把它耳朵摇掉它也听得到把它眼球挖出来他就看不到</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="12">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>孙耀中</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>03:31:18.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>03:31:18.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>8</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Well done. He should have bitten his neck!</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Well done. He should have bitten his neck!</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="13">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Helen Trang</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>00:21:57.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>00:21:57.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>2</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>7</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">We support freedom, democracy for HongKong 🤝💪</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>We support freedom, democracy for HongKong 🤝💪</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="14">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Jinyu Li</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-06</published_date>
               <published_time>23:48:03.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-06</final_date>
               <final_time>23:48:03.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>39</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>2</replies>
               <words>38</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Funny how people who call themselves “protesters” have all the rights to stab and shoot, and yet still be cheered up after. While the “polices” are blamed  for force reactions, even those reactions might only be for self-defense.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Funny how people who call themselves “protesters” have all the rights to stab and shoot, and yet still be cheered up after. While the “polices” are blamed  for force reactions, even those reactions might only be for self-defense.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="14.1">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>LokYin Yun</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-08</published_date>
               <published_time>08:41:29.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-08</final_date>
               <final_time>08:43:09.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>1</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <words>35</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">&amp;#39;all the right to stab and shoot&amp;#39; Give me an example of a protester shooting someone.&lt;br /&gt;Also the police lobbing tear gas at journalists or into people&amp;#39;s home is sure as sh*t not self defense.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>'all the right to stab and shoot' Give me an example of a protester shooting someone.
Also the police lobbing tear gas at journalists or into people's home is sure as sh*t not self defense.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="14.2">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Fistbeardthepirate</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-07</published_date>
               <published_time>22:29:00.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-07</final_date>
               <final_time>22:29:00.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>1</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <words>27</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">You assume he was a protester! Yet he attacked a pro-democracy councillor, Andrew Chiu.&lt;br /&gt;And I notice that SCMP has neglected to mention he is a democrat.</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>You assume he was a protester! Yet he attacked a pro-democracy councillor, Andrew Chiu.
And I notice that SCMP has neglected to mention he is a democrat.</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="15">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Chopper</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-06</published_date>
               <published_time>20:43:09.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-06</final_date>
               <final_time>20:43:09.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>35</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">The order of event....protests lawful or unlawful, riot after set-up road blocks, smash and set fire to shops,   enter shopping mail to hide,  riot police respond!!  Stop mess around with words and order of event!!</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>The order of event....protests lawful or unlawful, riot after set-up road blocks, smash and set fire to shops,   enter shopping mail to hide,  riot police respond!!  Stop mess around with words and order of event!!</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="16">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Liu Leo</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-06</published_date>
               <published_time>19:15:26.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-06</final_date>
               <final_time>19:15:26.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>13</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">A pro-democracy leader got one of his pro-democracy ears bitten off. How painful!</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>A pro-democracy leader got one of his pro-democracy ears bitten off. How painful!</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="17">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Lisa Cleary</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-06</published_date>
               <published_time>19:00:13.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-06</final_date>
               <final_time>19:00:13.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>22</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">I am really praying that Hong Kong officials politicians can bring negations to their young people that will end this desperate situation</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>I am really praying that Hong Kong officials politicians can bring negations to their young people that will end this desperate situation</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="18">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>Ray Mak</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-06</published_date>
               <published_time>18:36:54.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-06</final_date>
               <final_time>18:36:54.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>1</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>2</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Sad case</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Sad case</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="19">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>carry k</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-06</published_date>
               <published_time>17:13:46.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-06</final_date>
               <final_time>17:13:46.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>13</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">fuck all those chinese and free Hong Kong Shi is a mo fu</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>fuck all those chinese and free Hong Kong Shi is a mo fu</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
         <async_comment id="20">
            <comment_info>
               <commentator>yan yan</commentator>
               <published_date>2019-11-06</published_date>
               <published_time>16:12:08.000Z</published_time>
               <final_date>2019-11-06</final_date>
               <final_time>16:12:08.000Z</final_time>
               <likes>0</likes>
               <rating>none</rating>
               <replies>0</replies>
               <words>2</words>
            </comment_info>
            <comment_content>
               <original_script name="Roman">Free scotland！</original_script>
            </comment_content>
            <comment_content_initial>Free scotland！</comment_content_initial>
         </async_comment>
      </youtube_video>
   </asynchronous>
</co3h>
